{
    "subject": "resource/The_Trusts_Arena",
    "predicate": "property/opened",
    "object": "2004-09-11",
    "human_readable": "The Trusts Arena was opened on September 11, 2004.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.970737874507904,
            "question": "What is the name of the arena that was opened on September 11, 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9202154874801636,
            "question": "When was the Trusts Arena opened?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8712186217308044,
            "question": "In what year did the Trusts Arena open?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076242208480835,
            "question": "Who might have been involved in opening the Trusts Arena?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7952384948730469,
            "question": "What is the significance of September 11th in relation to the Trusts Arena?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6547181606292725,
            "question": "What events might be held at the Trusts Arena?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6353800892829895,
            "question": "Where is the Trusts Arena located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6029837131500244,
            "question": "What kind of impact did the opening of the Trusts Arena have on the community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5597248673439026,
            "question": "Are there any notable events that have taken place at the Trusts Arena?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5477988123893738,
            "question": "Is the Trusts Arena a sports venue?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Trusts Arena was opened on September 11, 2004.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2540_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events that have taken place at the Trusts Arena?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2540_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of impact did the opening of the Trusts Arena have on the community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2540_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the Trusts Arena located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2540_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2540_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that \"The Trusts Arena was opened on September 11, 2004.\" The documents mention that the arena was opened by then Prime Minister Helen Clark on 11 September 2004 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2540/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2540/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"The Arena was opened by then Prime Minister of New Zealand Helen Clark on 11 September 2004,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}